Gather around my faithful crew
I've got a message just for you
Wear your sparkles, bring your wigs
Tonight we're dancing with wild jigs
We're not just followers, we're free
And get cultish breeze
Let's start the sh-
Your carers join the tribe with neon flares
Echoes of funky bass and beat
Our wild sermon can't be beat
Step by step, let's break the mold
In this laughter
hands up shout it loud we're the wildest in the crowd need chance and crazy moods in this cold the
offering from cataracts glaucoma or blurred vision did you know your eyesight can be
and I'm a million different people from one day to the next I can change my mode no no no no
I don't want to totally tell you guys his history, like his dating history.
Have you ever done this to other women besides me?
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
I fucking, I don't know.
No, no, no.
When he rages out and like, he's calling them names.
I don't know.
I'm just telling the chat, I'm just telling the chat what I've witnessed from this guy.
He's disappeared for a certain amount of time and then he comes back like every third
like that's what Carl is. He's like the Jeepers Creepers. Like, uh, no, I've literally okay. The first time he came back after having a like a period of absence. He came back in like May of 2023. I documented it. And he he raged and that was when him and D gas had a falling out big time. And that was a huge moment right there.
Listen, I really don't appreciate you being around this fucking area right now. We don't give a fuck. Go live, you know
Yeah, so
Crawlful it wants to start going live again. Yeah, and you know, he's in here like sparring about it acting erratic
I saw him on psych issue earlier. He's drunk as fuck like that's the thing though
It's like every time I go live after hear about it like Carl me and you are not together
We're just fucking friends and that was the reason in the first place
I didn't want to ever go forward with you because I don't like controlling people at fucking off
So I have to deal with the wrath of fucking I literally made one comment that some guy that delivered my like
Washer dryer here was pretty good-looking and I keep getting continued messages about him go live your life
You're drunk 50 on 20 this and that and I'm like, okay. I'm just living my fucking life next thing
I know I'm getting messages like
Control Carl close not my boyfriend. Listen Carl if you're not interested in me
I don't care whether you are not or you are I always said we're cool. We can be friends
I this is the reason it never got anywhere like stop this
I tell you he was crazy be there
Look ladies. I'll be there when I go live. He's trying. He thinks you can get me jealous
This is another raging demon. So if you can't get me fucking jealous
You make yourself like and then he's like beta you're 20 see your your 25 going on 50 or 50 going on 25
Sorry putting me down all the fucking time. I think this is just like
And like, as soon as I fucking made a mention about some cute guy that delivered shit to my house, come on, Chill.
Alright, you guys, just do the work. I don't care. Put your pictures on whatever you want.
Okay, there's no problem. No problem.
He did it. He did it first. Don't bother me, though.
He did it first. He did it first.
Hey, I'm just here to chill. Go ahead, send it right in your mouth like you always do.
Nah, I'm just wondering why you always do it.
No, nigga! Shut the fuck up!
What the fuck up everybody, are you guys on your pictures now?
This ain't your platform.
This ain't yours.
Yeah, whatever. I just don't need anyone to fucking control me message me. Tell me and criticize me. Tell me. Look at what you're doing. Look what you did last night. You said this. I like I got this message three times already by Carl. Oh, so go date the guy that did a delivery. Look how disparate you are. You want to date a guy who did a delivery for you. I never ever fucking even said that. I just said some dude that delivered my refrigerator was fucking hot. That's it. You know,
and ironically he asked for my Instagram now have we talked no but it was a compliment you know
for me because I was like wow you know somebody that actually found attractive likes me so it was
like you know saying that on my panel I didn't tell him personally or privately we were I was
talking about on my panel he listened to that pisses him off messages me go be with that guy
Oh my gosh, look at, look at what's here.
I want everything from me.
Bita, we can be together.
Bita, we're made in heaven.
We're made in destiny.
I love you forever.
See, he leaves every time.
You're a fucking liar.
Yes.
Thank you.
Sam, you can still catch me right back.
Every time you lie, I'm gonna fucking say the truth, okay?
deal with like
Bullshit from like raging demon and then I got a deal with the rage of fucking like Carl when he's like
I don't fucking give a fuck. I'm trying to live my fucking life
If you're a cool person you can be my like friend for life
And you never know where it might take it
But if I see red flags, I'm already like what the fuck I do fucking nothing like I can't even tell a story
Or say anything without the next like next morning people message me. I didn't like that that made me upset
I'm jealous. I'm butthurt rookie streamer bitch
You're a fucking rookie fucking like sitting here telling me that I'm like 50 going like 50 going on 25
Look at how you're acting and mature
You act like you I
Oh god, I want to keep my mouth shut. I'm gonna get that's where I started getting mean just keep pressing me
Keep pressing me say one more fucking thing Carl. Keep pressing me. All right, and I'll fucking open my mouth
So fucking wide open you're gonna be fucking leaving the internet for another six months
So, um
He said he said he went on and he went on a rampage
He went on Jay Savage panel told people I do crack cocaine. I'm this I'm that he went on
Elders and said some stuff and then he messaged me the next day
And he said he was sorry and he will never happen again
And he won't contact me again, and he didn't and it was for six months now when the raging demon stuff went down
he came back and he was like I saw this shit and it's fucked up you don't deserve it and I was like
okay that's nice like he actually stood to his word and he's nothing like rage I saw it like
Carl was bad um Raging Demon is horrible and I still stand on that Raging Demon is horrible
Well, it's not even as bad, but it's still the same concept. I do not want a fucking boyfriend
I don't want a relationship. You can do whatever the fuck you want. I don't want anything
All right, nothing. Yeah, he's looking like a narcissist right now. Yeah, I'm just all good
I look like a narcissist are you just leaving back listening like oh, they're talking about me. I'm getting attention
I'm going live soon
I literally, when I leave this shit, I literally like leave this shit.
I had to step away from my puppies, my dogs, get feed them, take them outside, make sure
they're good.
And then I come back and then I hear my moniker name, not real name, moniker name.
I said Carl.
Yeah, that's mine. That's not my real name. It's my moniker name. Hey
So how am I a narcissist
Did the Harvard stem cell Institute just find a way to restore crystal clear 2020 vision without glasses contact?
I soon your message you mean jealous about a guy that delivered my washer and dryer like fucking three-time
Get married
I never said that I never said that
Why are you even messaging me about some washer dryers?
I've never said why you've been being married.
Don't gaslight me. I'll pull up this shit right now.
Don't gaslight me. I'll pull this shit right now.
I said be married? I said be married? Really?
Yeah, you're like, oh, you met this guy. I hope you're happy.
You like, uh, led me on.
Yeah, baby. Nice to meet you. And then Carl Foyle. You know the foil that you smoke crack on that Carl Foyle on the panel?
No, no, no, no. That's Carl Foyle. No, no, no. Of course she would say that. She wants to degrade me.
Yeah. Because she hates me. Because you want it because she loves me so much. That's why.
Okay. Well, what's your name?
Carl Foyle.
Okay. Well, that's not like full is not foil. Yeah. Yeah. But she wants to degrade me.
She wants to put me down because she loves me so much. Well, you know, you're still here
and seem to maybe maybe like it and she likes it. And let's fucking go.
Why don't you talk about your team? You got arrested on this team.
I've never done that that's our own way back some of your other fucking streams
Why don't you go fucking like listen? This is the problem with you. You think this is a fucking competition. Okay, you know
Pepper for neuropathy my tingling and numbness in the legs and feet that never stopped is finally gone
Chad is so funny.
That's so funny.
They went through rocks.
I have it on stream.
I got hit with the rock.
They were starting fires over there.
Yeah.
Women have to disagree with the peaceful protest part.
Huh?
Yeah!
They went through rocks!
Chad said, I'm just reading Chad.
I can't I cannot argue with with 1,500 people. It's kind of hard. They win every time because they'll just roast me
Yeah, but there's it's still the act of throwing rocks throw a rock and then they shoot the tear gas
That's just how it works. No, I saw what you're talking about
While everybody was flying through their eyes
Yeah
But is it yeah, why?
Why not?
Why?
That's not a good reason.
I hear all the voices that you hear, all the people that I hear post that thing again.
Yeah, but then you just sound like a Karen at that point.
Those types are the right side of history.
No, they're not, because they never did anything.
History proves that it doesn't do anything.
I got it? Huh?
It's not, because it's like...
I take things with a grain of salt and I use my education.
Did you graduate? Because I graduated with honors.
I graduated from UCLA. Where'd you graduate from?
Okay. Okay, colleague.
So then you would be able to tell me in an educated way.
See, that's just ignorant. You're just being ignorant at that point.
That's okay.
But it's not. They're American citizens, just like me and you.
I can't hear you because you're mumbling.
What? Yeah, they're protecting America.
They're protecting America, guy.
You're white. You have no say.
I'm Hispanic. I'm Cuban.
I'm Cuban. Mine is going to swim here 90 miles, cracker.
White person my uncle's I'm Cuban. I'm Cuban white person white person
We don't need people to stand we don't need white people stand up for us. We're not victims racist your racist your racist
You're racist. You're being racist. I bet you're gonna say who's gonna pick the crops right sounds like who's gonna pick the cotton
But it sounds like who's gonna pick the kind every time a Democrat says who's gonna pick the crops
It sounds like he's gonna pick the cotton. It's just racism. It's it's it's
racism disguise
It's slavery
I'm Hispanic I'm Hispanic you're not
Wait, where is your say?
Where's your say my grandma my my my dad swim 90 miles
90 because I don't care. I voted for Trump. I voted for this. I voted for this. I voted for this. I voted for this
Yes, yes see popcorn
I don't have a more famous. I have a million followers on YouTube. I don't care
I'm getting doughnose right now. I don't care. I'm making money off. Thanks for the dough knows. Thank you for the dough knows
I appreciate you
You're making me money right now cracker white person greasy white person your wife. You're embarrassing yourself
I am human racist
You're racist!
Now she's calling people monkeys, you're racist!
I am a Cuban racist!
I'm Cuban!
My dad's a marito!
Mariel!
My dad's a Mariel, sir!
My dad's a Mariel!
Okay?
You're a Mariel!
I already got the reaction!
I made three G's just now.
$1,700 donut right now.
$1,700 donut. Look at the chat.
Dude, I'm very famous.
I don't need it.
Oh my god, all two people.
Look at my chat. They're clowning you.
No, I'm not.
They found your Facebook, by the way.
I don't care.
She assaulted me! She assaulted me! Ha ha ha! Alright, rest her!
Rest her!
Wait a minute, I need to get some energy drinks. I'm going to go to the store and get energy drinks.
I'm trying to wake up. I'm feeling very well. Okay, I'll talk to you soon.